watchtime.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy › WatchTime - USA's No.1 Watch Magazine

WatchTime.com (“We”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

By using WatchTime.com (“our site”), you are consenting to this Privacy Policy and to have your personal data transferred to and/or processed in the United States in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, except in the case of data transfers from the EEA and Switzerland, which are covered under the U.S.-EU and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks. The data collection practices set out in this Privacy Policy are for the primary purpose of fulfilling your orders and providing customer support. Please do not use WatchTime.com if you do not agree with this policy and any other policies listed on WatchTime.com.  WatchTime.com complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view WatchTime.com’s certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/

**A.              ****Information We Collect**

1\.              Non-Personally Identifiable Information

When you enter WatchTime.com, we collect certain non-personally identifiable information through the use of cookies and other similar technologies. Our use of such technologies is set forth in the [**Watchtime.com Cookie Disclosure**](http://www.watchtime.com/watchtime-com-cookie-disclosure/) which is incorporated by reference into this Privacy Policy.

2\.              Personally Identifiable Information

Many of the services offered on WatchTime.com are only made available if we have certain information about you.  To access these services, you will, from time to time, be asked to submit personal information about yourself.  We may collect and process the following personal information related to our services:

  * Registration information.  In registering for WatchTime.com, we require certain contact information (including your name, year of birth, e-mail address, physical address and IP address.) We use this to contact you regarding orders and other notices.

  * Information to fulfill your order.  When placing an order online at WatchTime.com, we collect your name, phone number, shipping address, billing address, and personal payment information.  This information is used to process and fulfill any orders you may make.

  * Support. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence and record conversations for training and/or monitoring purposes.

  * Surveys. We may from time to time ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes.  You do not have to respond to these surveys and may opt out of future e-mails by clicking a link at the bottom of the e-mail or by simply e-mailing us at office@watchtime.com.

3.              Privacy of Children and Sensitive Consumer Information

WatchTime.com is designed for those 13 years of age or older.  WatchTime.com does not knowingly collect information from anyone under the age of 13. At the time of registration you will be asked for your year of birth.

Except for collecting payment information in connection with purchases, WatchTime.com does not knowingly obtain or store any Sensitive Consumer Information, such as Social Security Numbers and other government Issued identifiers; insurance plan numbers; financial account numbers; information that describes the precise real-time geographic location of an individual; or precise information related to health or medical conditions.

If we are made aware that we have received information from anyone under the age of 13 or Sensitive Consumer Information in violation of this Privacy Policy, we will use reasonable efforts to locate and remove that information from our records.

**B.              Use of Information Collected**

1\.              Primary Purpose of Information Collected

The information and data collected by WatchTime.com is primarily for the purposes of:

  * Processing your orders effectively;
  * Ensuring that content from our site is presented to you in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
  * Notifying you about changes to our service and policies; and
  * Responding to your customer support inquiries.

2\.              Mailings

WatchTime.com may periodically contact you using information supplied to the site.  You may opt out of receiving certain communications, such as newsletters or other e-mails, by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of such e-mails or by e-mailing [office@watchtime.com](mailto:office@watchtime.com).

3\.              Access to and Ability to Correct Personal Data

You have the right to review your personal data held by WatchTime.  You also have the right to modify, correct, change or update your personal information or cause your personal information to be deleted from WatchTime.com’s database upon request. All requests to view, change, update, or delete your personal information may be made via e-mail at [office@watchtime.com](mailto:office@watchtime.com) or via postal mail to Ebner Publishing International, Inc., 274 Madison Avenue, Suite 804, New York, NY 10016.

**C.              Disclosure of your Personal Information**

1\.              Third Parties

Except as provided in the Privacy Policy, WatchTime will not sell, rent, transfer, or transfer your personal information to third parties without obtaining further consent from you. WatchTime may sell to third parties the right to offer products or services by email or regular mail to our current or prospective customers, our mailing list members and our site visitors. These third parties will offer their products or services to you under their brand name. We will transfer or provide access to your actual email address (physical, email or IP) to third parties and every communication from third parties to you will be approved by us by WatchTime and sent by us.  You may also opt-out of us emailing offers to you on our behalf or on behalf of third-parties at any time by e-mailing office@watchtime.com.

2\.              Compliance with Law

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, as required by law or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our web site.  Furthermore, we may share your personal information when we believe it is necessary to protect our interests or our property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through WatchTime.com or using our name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm.  This may include, but is not limited to, sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

3\.              Service Providers

We may employ service providers and other companies and individuals to perform functions and provide services on our behalf (e.g. credit card processing, shipping, insurance).  These entities may have access to your personal information to the extent needed to perform their functions and also to provide you with the services that you have requested, but these service providers shall be contractually obligated not use this information for any other purpose. We will share our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use with every service providers in order to make sure that they comply.

4.              Ownership Changes

If the ownership of all or substantially all of the WatchTime.com business, or individual business units owned by WatchTime.com were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations, without prior notice to you. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the provisions of any the current privacy policy.

**D.              Security **

We have implemented reasonable measures to protect the information we collect and store, taking into consideration the types of risks we face and the reasonable protections available to us. The user data is stored in password protected and encrypted locations that can only be accessed by authorized employees who have signed non-disclosure agreements and whose ID is associated with each individual database access. No third party will ever have access to these databases. The databases are located in the U.S. and in Germany. However, no method protecting information is 100% secure, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**E.               Privacy Practices of Third Parties**

When you click on links or advertising, third parties may collect information from you and place their own cookies or other technological devices on your Internet browser, independent of WatchTime.com.  We have no control over these third parties and no responsibility for the technologies they employ.  To learn how a particular web site collects and uses your information, you should read the privacy policy of that website.

**F.              Changes to Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently and at least each time you submit personal information to WatchTime.com. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here at [Privacy Policy URL], by e-mail, or by means of a notice on our homepage. The date of the most recent revisions will also appear on this page. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your interactions with WatchTime.com.

**G.             Questions**

For questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy please e-mail us at [office@watchtime.com](mailto:office@watchtime.com).  Alternatively, you can write to us at: Ebner Publishing International, Inc., 274 Madison Avenue, Suite 804, New York, NY 10016.

**H.**              **Privacy Complaints by European Union and Swiss Citizens**

In compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, WatchTime,com commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Experts Exchange, LLC at:

Mail: Ebner Publishing International, Inc., Attn: Stephen Brown, 274 Madison Avenue, Suite 804, New York, NY 10016.

Email: office@watchtime.com

Telephone: +1-646-742-0740

WatchTime.com has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by WatchTime.com, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints for more information and to file a complaint.

Last Updated: October, 2013

See also:
